(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T09:47:00.213310",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
興奮すっぞ！ 宇宙へGO!
Get excited! To space, let's go!
最先端の"夢中"をどう！
Grab the cutting-edge "obsession"!
この手に掴むよ
I'll hold it in my own hands.
素っ頓狂に笑ってタイ！
Laugh out loud wildly!
チンプンカンプンはなれこだい！
Nonsense is a thing of the past!
I can't get no satisfaction
退屈は
Boredom
石になる
turns into stone
重くて落ちいちゃうまえに
Before it gets too heavy and drags me down,
Let's fly high
ワクワクの
Spread our thrilling
羽根広げ
wings wide open
次の世界へ行こう
and head to the next world!
可能性のドアは施錠されたまま
The door of possibilities remains locked,
やれやれ…今度も壁ブチやぶる
Good grief... I'll smash through the wall again!
今だ！限界×突破
Now! Break the limits!
叫べ！へのかへのカッパ
Shout out! It's a piece of cake!
無敵のオイラがそこで待っている
The invincible me is waiting right there!
ドラゴンボール超
Dragon Ball Super
全王様もオッタマゲーー！！
Even the Grand Zeno will be blown away!!
想像すっぞ！愉快な今日！
Let's imagine! A joyful today!
天丼☆天気 気分は“上”
Rice bowl, weather, mood is "top notch"
夢見りゃ叶うよ
If you dream, it will come true
大根戦だ かかってこい！
Daicon battle! Come and get me!
バッタンキューとひねってポイ！
Knocked out and twisted away!
I can't get more satisfaction
信じれば
If you believe
手の中に
In your hands
渦巻くカメハメの波
A swirling Kamehame wave
Let's make it
悲しみを砕く時
When sadness cracks apart
キミも戦士だろう
You're a warrior too, aren't you?
意外性を秘めたヤツが生き残る
The one who hides unpredictability survives
マジかよ… 100倍 やばいサバイバル
Seriously... 100 times, a dangerous survival
行くぞ！限界×突破
Let's go! Break the limits!
パワー全開！やっぱ…
Power full throttle! As expected...
秒速 進化のバトルが見せばさ
If you show a battle of split-second evolution
ドラゴンボール超 破壊神だけヘチャムクレ～！
Dragon Ball Super! Even the God of Destruction...
はーい！というわけで、1曲目は
Hi there! So, that was our first song,
限界×突破サバイバーをお届けしました！どう？
"Genkai Toppa Survivor"! How was it?
かっこよかった？シオンの今日のビーム！
Look cool? Shion's beam today!
みんなちゃんときらっかな？
Did everyone take a direct hit properly?
背筋で誕生日を迎えましたー！
I welcomed my birthday straight and proud!
今日はですね、紫シオン バースデーアニソンライブということで、
Today is Murasaki Shion's Birthday Anison Live,
アニソンメインでガンガン歌っていくよー！
so we're gonna sing lots of anime songs!
ハッシュタグは「#紫シオン生誕ライブ2024」で
Please tweet lots with the hashtag
たくさんツイートしてくださいね！
"#MurasakiShionBirthdayLive2024"!
そして、なんとこのステージ…… 超かわいい！
And, amazingly, this stage... is super cute!
見て、めっちゃよくない？
Look, isn't it super nice?
上にね、くまちゃんがいるのわかる？
Can you see there's a little bear up top?
おめめがね、キョロキョロでね、超かわいいんですよ。
Its eyes are darting around, super cute.
めっちゃかわいい！本当に素敵なステージに立たせていただいちゃいました。
I'm so glad to stand on such a wonderful stage.
後半に重大告知もあるし、
There are major announcements in the second half,
なんとゆーかね、楽しみだね！
how should I put it, something to look forward to!
ライブ終わった後にも楽しみがあるので、最後まで絶対に逃がさないでください！
There's fun waiting even after the live ends!
まだまだいろんなアニソンを、いろんなゲストの方と一緒に歌っていくので、一緒に楽しんでいこうー！
We'll sing more anime songs with various guests!
それでは次の曲、どうぞ！
And now, our next song, here it is!
おいでファンタジー 好きさミステリー
Come, fantasy, love, mystery
君の若さ 隠さないで
Don't hide your youth
不思議したくて 冒険したくて
I want a mystery, I want an adventure
誰もみんな ウズウズしてる
Everyone is itching for one
大人のフリして あきらめちゃう
If you pretend to be adult and give up
奇跡の謎など 解けないよ
Things like mysteries and miracles can't be solved
もっとワイルドに もっとたくましく 生きてごらん
Live wilder, live stronger
ロマンティックあげるよ ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance! I'll give you romance!
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance!
トキメク胸に
To your pounding heart...
キラキラ光った夢をあげるよ
I'll give you a sparkling, shining dream!
いつかワンダフル きっとビューティフル
Someday wonderful, surely beautiful...
人のジャングル迷い込んで
Getting lost in the jungle of people,
スリルしたくて 幸せしたくて
wanting thrills, wanting happiness—
何故かみんなソワソワしてる
for some reason, everyone is on edge.
思ったとおりに叫ばなきゃ
You've got to shout just as you feel,
願いは空まで届かない
or your wish won't reach the sky!
もっとセクシーに もっと美しく 生きてごらん
Try living sexier, try living more beautifully!
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance!
ホントの涙見せてくれたら
If you show me your true tears,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance!
淋しい心
Your lonesome heart...
やさしく包んで 愛をあげるよ
I'll gently wrap it and give you my love!
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance!
ホントの勇気見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance!
トキメク胸に
To your pounding heart...
キラキラ光った夢をあげるよ
I'll give you a sparkling, shining dream!
とっておき ふくつのこころ もって
Carrying an utmost indomitable spirit,
高い テンガン山 越えて 行こう
let's cross over the high Mt. Tengan!
だれを ゲット かな？ どこで 出会う かな？
Who will I catch? Where will I meet them?
ワクワク気分 まるで ひみつきち さ
This thrilling feeling is just like a secret base!
新しい 町
To a new town,
僕らは 進む
we march forward
輝く 時 の 中 で
amidst shining times.
イエイ イエイ イエイ イエイ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yay!!
甘くないさ バトルは いつだって
Battles are never easy, anytime!
からい？ にがい？ しぶい？ すっぱいね？
Spicy? Bitter? Astringent? Sour?
生きてるんだ だから 感じよう
We're alive, so let's feel it all together!
イエイ イエイ イエイ イエイ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yay!!
アクア ジェット で 吹き飛ばし てけ
Blow it all away with Aqua Jet,
モヤモヤ気分 切り払いして ロッククライム 乗り越えたら
clear away the gloomy mood with Rock Climb, and once we climb over—
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! みんな GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! Everyone, GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
長い 長い 旅 の 途中 に いって も
Even in the middle of a long, long journey,
数え切れない バトル 思い出せば
when you remember the countless battles,
時空 を 超えて 僕らは 会える
crossing space and time, we can meet again.
まぶしい みんな の 顔
Everyone's dazzling faces—
イエイ イエイ イエイ イエイ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yay!!
まだまだ未熟 毎日が修行
Still inexperienced, everyday is training!
勝っても負けても最後は握手さ
Win or lose, it always ends in a handshake.
なつきチェッカー ごめんねゼロ
Friendship checker? Sorry, it reads zero!
ホントに CRY CRY クライネ!!
Really, cry, cry, cry-ne!!
きらめく瞳 ダイヤかパール
Sparkling eyes like diamonds or pearls!
とって置き ふくろのところ もって
With your last resort, a steadfast heart
高いテンガング山越えて行こう
Let's go cross the tall Mt. Coronet!
だれをゲットかな? どこで出会うかな?
Who will we get? Where will we meet?
ワクワク気分 まるで ひみつききち
I'm excited, as if it's a secret base.
新しい町僕らは進む
A new town, we'll proceed there
輝く時の中で
During shining times...
イエイ・イエイ・イエイ・イエ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yeah!!
甘くないさ バトルはいつでも
Battles are never sweet!
からい? にがい? しぶい? すっぱいね?
Spicy? Bitter? Dry? Sour, right?
生きてるんだ だから感じよう いっしょに
We are alive, so feel together!
イエイ・イエイ・イエイ・イエ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yeah!!
アクアジェットで 吹き飛ばしてけ
Blast away with Aqua Jet
モヤモヤ気分 きりばらしして
And Defog away our clouded spirits!
ロッククライム ほら 乗り越えたら
Rock Climb - look, if we can climb over...
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! みんな GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
Good, Good, Smile!! Everyone Good, Good, Smile!!
過去と未来 僕らはめざす
Past and future, we aim towards
誓ったあの場所へ
That place we pledged.
イエイ・イエイ・イエイ・イエ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yeah!!
甘くないさ バトルはいつでも
Battles are never sweet!
からい? にがい? しぶい? すっぱいね?
Spicy? Bitter? Dry? Sour, right?
生きてるんだ だから感じよう いっしょに
We are alive, so feel together!
イエイ・イエイ・イエイ・イエ!!
Yay, yay, yay, yeah!!
アクアジェットで 吹き飛ばしてけ
Blast away with Aqua Jet
モヤモヤ気分 きりばらしして
And Defog away our clouded spirits!
ロッククライム ほら 乗り越えたら
Rock Climb - look, if we can climb over...
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! みんな GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
Good, Good, Smile!! Everyone Good, Good, Smile!!
ねぇ 君たちの夢って 何かな?
Hey, what is everyone's dream?
ポケモン151匹ゲット!
Getting 151 Pokémon!
あら、私と同じ!
Oh, the same as me!
え~? おとなのくせに 変なの~
Huh? That's weird for an adult!
なによ~ いけな~い?
What? Isn't that allowed?
いけなくないけどさぁ…
It's not that it's not allowed, but...
ねぇ 君たちさ 他にはどんな夢があるの?
Hey, everyone, what other dreams do you have?
う~んとね もうひとつのゆめはね…
Uhm, well, another dream is...
早くおとなになりたいんだ
I want to become an adult quickly!
え?どうして?
Eh? Why?
早くおとなになりたいの こどもって楽しいじゃん
I want to become an adult quickly because being a kid is fun,
でもね なんだかなってみたい
but somehow, I want to try being one.
じゃ今度は私のユメ 言うわね…
Well then, next, I'll tell you my dream.
もう一度こどもに戻ってみたい
I want to go back to being a child once more.
え~?なんで~?
Eh~? Why~?
もう一度こどもに戻ってみたいの おとなでいいのに
I want to go back to being a child once more, even though I'm already an adult.
一日だけでもなれないかな?
Can't I become one, even for just a day?
なれっこないよ~ もういじわるぅ
You can't! Stop teasing me!
むかしわたしが まだこどもだったころ
Back when I was still a child,
ポケットにいれてた たくさんのたからもの
all the treasures I kept in my pocket...
いまでもときどき かおをのぞかせるのよ
I still peek at them from time to time.
それって もしかして ピカチュウ?
Could that perhaps be... Pikachu?
さあ なんでしょうね?
Well, who knows?
むかしのこども いまのこども
Children of the past, children of the present,
ポケットのなかみは いつだって
what's inside the pocket is always...
おとこのこでも おんなのこでも
Whether you're a boy or a girl,
ポケットのなかみは だれだってファンタジー
what's inside everyone's pocket is a fantasy!
もしもおとなになったんなら なにしてみたい?
If I were to become an adult, what would I want to do?
こことあそんであげるんだ
I'd play with the kids!
やっぱりあそびたいんだ
So you still want to play, huh?
でもね しごともちょっとするよ
But you know, I'd also work a little bit!
あのね 私がもしもね… もう一度こどもに戻れたなら
Um, you know, if I could go back to being a child...
なにしたいの?
What would you want to do?
あってみたいひとがいるの
There's someone I'd like to meet.
え~だれなの~?
Eh~, who could that be?
一日だけでも あえないかな?
Can't I meet them, even for just a day?
あ!はつこいのひとだ!
Ah, it's my first love!
あっさり~!
Spot on!
むかしわたしが いつかであおうと
Back when I was hoping to meet them someday,
ポケットにいれてた てづくりのプレゼント
the handmade present I put in my pocket...
いつでもときどき かおがあかくなるのよ
My face still turns red whenever I remember it.
プレゼントわたせなかったの?
Did you manage to give them the present?
さあどうだったかしら?
Well, who knows how it went?
むかしのこども いまのこども
Children of the past, children of the present,
ポケットのなかみは いつだって
what's inside the pocket is always...
おとこのこでも おんなのこでも
Whether you're a boy or a girl,
ポケットのなかみは
what's inside the pocket...
ポケットの なかみは だれだって ファンタジー
The contents of everyone's pocket are a fantasy
ラン ラン ラン ラン ラン ラン ラン ラ ラン
La la la la la la la...
おーい！ もしもしー！
Hey! Hello!
もしもし？
Hello?
あれ？ ここ、は… えっ！？
Huh? Where is this... Eh?!
えっ！？ あ、あなたは…！
Eh?! Ah, you are...!
あ、こんにちは。
Ah, hello.
サトシ声優の松本梨香です！
I'm Satoshi's voice actress, Rica Matsumoto!
リカさんがなんで目の前に！？ て、ここどこ！？
Why is Rica-san right in front of me?! W-Where is this?!
えへ、ここはシオンちゃんの夢の中です。
Hehe, here is Shion-chan's dream.
えー！？私がリカさんに会いたすぎて、その願いが夢の中で実現したってこと！？やったー！ずっと会いたかったです！
Eh?! My wish to meet Rica-san came true in a dream?! Yay! I've always wanted to meet you!
いやぁ、嬉しいな、そんな風に言ってくれて。
Aw, I'm so happy you say that.
やばい、いま夢が叶ってる！実は私の人生の初恋がリカさんの演じてるキャラクターでして…あの、好きです！
Oh no, my dream is coming true! Actually, my first crush in life was the character played by Rica-san... Um, I love you!
すごい「好きです」なんて気持ちを伝えてくれてどうもありがとう。とっても嬉しいです。
Thank you so much for telling me your feelings like "I love you". I'm so happy.
ひゃ、ちょっと、え、いま…めっちゃついです！おしっこ…
Hya, wait, eh, right now... I'm sweating so much! I need to pee...
あっ、はい！なんかおトイレ行きたいみたいになってる。大丈夫です？
Ah, yes! It feels like I need to go to the bathroom. Are you okay?
ちょっと、あの…ひとつお願いがありまして…
Um, well... I have one request...
はい、なんでしょう？
Yes, what is it?
もしよかったらなんですけど、私、誕生日を迎えまして…
If it's alright, I recently celebrated my birthday...
えー！おめでとう！
Ee! Happy birthday!
お祝いの言葉をいただけると…
If I could receive your congratulations...
もちろん です！
Of course!
行きますよ、じゃあ！ はい！シオン、お誕生日おめでとう！
Here we go then! Yes! Shion, happy birthday!
わあー！ありがとうございます！もう人生この一緒に悔いはないです！ありがとうございます！
Waah! Thank you so much! I have no regrets in life now! Thank you so much!
ねぇ、本当に…こちらこそありがとう。
Yeah, really... Thank you too.
そのあとマルシ…ちょっと、落ち着きます。
After that... I'll calm down a bit.
リカさん！よかったら私と一緒に歌を歌ってくれませんか？
Rica-san! If you'd like, won't you sing a song with me?
もちろん です！
Of course!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
緊張する…！それでは…聞いてください。「ハイタッチ！」
I'm so nervous...! Then please listen. "High Touch!"
けんか なかなおり また けんか
Fighting, making up, fighting again
言いたい こと いっぱい ある けど
There are so many things I want to say, but
いちばん は ……
Above all...
「 いてくれて ありがとう ！ 」
"Thank you for being here!"
旅 は みちづれ 世 は なさけ
A journey needs companions, the world needs kindness
わかった よう な 顔 し てる けど
Though I put on a knowing face
ほんとう は ……
Truly...
「 いてくれて うれしい ！ 」
"I'm so glad you're here!"
ナイス パートナー ！
Nice partner!
ナイス ライバル ！
Nice rival!
おして あげる よ
I'll give you a push
ひっぱっ て あげる
I'll pull you along
見あげる 太陽 なん だか まぶしく て
Looking up at the sun, somehow it's so dazzling
うまく いったら ハイタッチ ！
If things go well, high touch!
へこん じゃ って も もとどおり ！
Even if we get down, back to normal!
いっしょ なら ば ……
If we're together...
あきらめる の は 早い ぜ go go go !
Giving up is way too early! GO GO GO!
ねらい さだめ バブル こうせん ！
Aiming carefully, bubble beam!
たより に なる ポッチャマ だ けど
Though Piplup is dependable,
ときどき は ……
Sometimes...
はずれ ちゃっ て めっちゃ ピンチ ！
It misses and we're in a huge pinch!
きあい こめ て 10まん ボルト ！
Putting all our spirit into 100,000 volts!
おれ の じまん ピカチュウ だ けど
Though Pikachu is my pride,
かんたん に ……
It's not like...
勝てる わけ じゃ ない ！
We can win easily!
ナイス パートナー ！
Nice partner!
ナイス ライバル ！
Nice rival!
声かけ あって フォロー しあえ ば
Calling out to each other, backing each other up,
思った とおり に わざ も 決まる ！
Just as we thought, our moves hit the mark!
きまりだす…！
Decided...!
うまくいったら ハイタッチ！
If things go well, high five!
きょうの勝利は 忘れない！
We won't forget today's victory!
いっしょ ならば…
As long as we're together...
どんな ピンチ も にげてく！
Any pinch will run away!
腕をのばし ハイタッチ！
Reach out your arms and high five!
笑顔いっぱい こころづよい！
Full of smiles, feeling strong!
いっしょ ならば…
As long as we're together...
つよいアイテも ウェルカム！ GO GO GO!
Even strong opponents are welcome! Go, go, go!
きょうも あしたも あさっても 旅はずっとつづいてくけど
Today, tomorrow, and the day after, the journey will keep going on, but
いつだって… すぐそばに その笑顔！
Whenever it is... that smile is always right by my side!
きたへ みなみへ にし ひがし
To the north, south, west, and east,
景色くるくる 変わるけど
The scenery spins and changes, but
どこにいたって… いつも その笑顔！
No matter where we are... that smile is always there!
ナイスパートナー！
Nice partner!
ナイスライバル！
Nice rival!
まもってくれるよ たすけてくれる
You protect me, you help me out.
ひろがる荒野に 道が まっすぐに
Across the expanding wilderness, the road goes straight,
空のしたで ハイタッチ！
Under the sky, high five!
ことばよりも わかりやすい！
Easier to understand than words!
いっしょ ならば… 夢に向かって とべるぜ！
If we're together... we can fly toward our dreams!
うまくいったら ハイタッチ！
If things go well, high five!
へこんじゃっても もとどおり！
Even if we get down, we bounce right back!
いっしょ ならば… あきらめるのは 早いぜ！ GO GO GO!
As long as we're together... giving up is too soon! Go, go, go!
うまくいったね ハイタッチ！
Things went well, high five!
バトルあいてと ハンドシェイク！
Handshake with our battle opponent!
いっしょ ならば… もっと遠くに 行けるぜ！ GO GO GO!
As long as we're together... we can go even further! Go, go, go!
GO GO GO! GO GO GO!
というわけでリカさんとデュエットさせていただきました！ハイタッチでした！
And that's why we did a duet with Rika-san! It was a high five!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
楽しかったね！
That was fun!
楽しかったです！リカさんの歌声隣で聴けて本当に幸せでした！
It was so fun! Hearing Rika-san's singing voice right beside me made me so happy!
いやそれは良かったです！シオンちゃんもとっても可愛かったです！
Well, I'm glad! Shion-chan was also super cute!
ありがとうございます！嬉しいです！
Thank you very much! I'm so happy!
改めてお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday once again!
こちらこそ今日はありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today as well!
やばい、そろそろライブ会場の私目が覚めそうです！
Oh no, it looks like my real self at the live venue is about to wake up!
まだリカさんとお話ししたいのに！
Even though I want to talk more with Rika-san!
このあとのライブもめちゃめちゃ頑張ってください！
Please do your absolute best in the rest of the live concert too!
ありがとうございます！リカさん本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you! Rika-san, thank you truly so much!
こちらこそありがとうございました！
Thank you so much as well!
ではライブ頑張ってきます！ありがとうございました！
Well then, I'll do my best at the live! Thank you!
応援してるよー！
I'm rooting for you!
いっせーのーせで踏み込むゴールライン 僕らは何もまだ知らぬ
Stepping onto the goal line all at once, we still know nothing at all.
一線越えて振り返るともういない 僕らは何もまだ知らぬ
Crossing the line and looking back, you're no longer there, and we still know nothing.
奪って奪って奪っていく
Taking, taking, taking it all away,
煌めく汗がこぼれるのさ
Glistening sweat spills over.
覚えてないこともたくさんあっただろう
There must have been so many things we don't even remember.
誰も彼もシルエット
Everyone, anyone is just a silhouette.
大事にしてたもの忘れたフリをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget the things we held so dear.
なにもないよ、笑えるさ
There's nothing wrong, we can laugh about it.
いっせーのーせで思い出そうね 僕らは何もかもを欲しがった
Let's remember all together: we wanted to have everything.
わかってるって、ああ気づいてるって
We understand, ah, we've realized it.
いっせーのーせで踏み込むゴールライン
Stepping over the goal line in one go,
僕らは何も何もまだ知らぬ
We still don't know anything at all.
一線越えて振り返るともうない
Crossing the line, looking back, it's gone.
僕らは何も何もまだ知らぬ
We still don't know anything at all.
うだってうだってうだっていく
Sweltering, sweltering, sweltering away...
流れる時と記憶 遠く遠く遠くになって
Flowing time and memories, getting farther away.
覚えてないことも たくさんあっただろう
There must be so much we don't remember.
誰も彼もシルエット
Everyone, every silhouette.
大事にしてたもの 忘れたふりをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget what we cherished.
なにもないよ 笑えるさ
There's nothing to fear, we can laugh.
いっせーのーせで 思い出す少年
Remembering the boy in one go,
僕らは何もかもを欲しがった
We wanted to have everything.
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる
Fluttering and fluttering around,
木の葉のように憂うことなく焦燥もなく過ごしていたいよ
Like leaves, living without worry or impatience.
覚えてないことも たくさんあったけど
There were many things we don't remember, but
きっとずっと変わらないものがあることを
Surely there are things that will never change,
教えてくれたあなたは 消える消えるシルエット
You taught me, the silhouette that never fades.
大事にしたいもの持って大人になるんだ
Holding what we cherish as we grow into adults.
どんな時も離さずに守り続けよう
Let's keep protecting it no matter what.
そしたらいつの日にか なにもかもを笑えるさ
Then someday, we can laugh at everything.
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる 木の葉が飛んでゆく
Fluttering and fluttering, the leaves fly away.
不思議だね いまの気持ち
It's strange, how I feel right now,
空から降ってきたみたい
Like it came falling from the sky.
特別な季節の色が とめきを見せるよ
The special seasonal colors show excitement.
初めて出会った時から
Ever since the first time we met,
予感に騒ぐ心のMelody
My heart's melody stirs with anticipation.
とめられない とまらない なぜ
Unstoppable, won't stop, but why?
届けて 切なさには
Reach out, to this bittersweet feeling
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Let's give it a name: "Snow halation".
想いが重なるまで待てずに
Not waiting until our feelings overlap,
悔しいけど好きって純情
It's frustrating, but this pure love says I love you.
微熱の中 ためらってちゃダメだね
In this mild fever, I can't hesitate.
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
I approve the courage to dive in! Start is near!
音もなく 気配もなく
Without a sound, without a trace,
静かに運命は変わる
Fate quietly changes.
これからの未来に 胸の鼓動が早くなる
My heartbeat quickens for the future ahead.
例えば困った時には
For instance, whenever you're in trouble,
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
I want to rush over and hold you tight.
どこにいてもどこでも Fly high
No matter where you are, fly high!
急いで いつの間にか大きくなりすぎた “True emotion”
Hurry, "True emotion" grew too big before I knew it.
不思議だね いまの気持ち
It's strange, the current feeling
空から降ってきたみたい
seems like it came falling from the sky,
特別な季節の色が とめきを見せるよ
the special colors of the season show excitement.
初めて出会った時から
Since the first time we met,
予感に騒ぐ心のMelody
the melody of our excited hearts...
とまれないとまらないな・ぜ
unstoppable, won't stop, why?
届けて 切なには名前をつけようか“Snow halation”
Let's name this pain "Snow halation."
想いが重なるまで待てずに
Don't wait until your feelings pile up,
悔しいけど好きって純情
it's frustrating, but it's pure love.
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In the midst of hesitation, you can't hold back,
飛び込む勇気に賛成
approve the courage to jump in,
まもなくStart!!
the start is near!
届けて 切なには名前をつけようか“Snow halation”
Let's name this pain "Snow halation."
想いが重なるまで待てずに
Don't wait until your feelings pile up,
悔しいけど好きって純情
it's frustrating, but it's pure love.
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In the midst of hesitation, you can't hold back,
飛び込む勇気に賛成
approve the courage to jump in,
まもなくStart!!
the start is near!
ONE PUNCH!
Kill shot!
参上！必勝！史上最強！！
Appearing! Certain victory! The supreme strongest!!
なんだってんだ？フラストレーション 俺は止まらない
What're ya saying? Frustration. I won't stop!
ONE PUNCH！完了！連戦連勝！
One punch! Complete! A succession of victories!
俺は勝つ！常に勝つ！圧勝！！
I always win! Complete victory!
Power! Get power! ギリギリ限界まで
Power! Get power! To the limit!
Hero 俺を讃える声や 喝采なんて欲しくはないさ
Hero, I don't want voices praising me or acclamation,
Hero だから人知れず悪と闘う
Hero, that's why I fight evil in secret.
Nobody knows who he is.
天覆い押し寄せる敵 俺は背を向けはしない
Enemies closing in, covering the sky, I won't turn my back on them!
Hero ならば揺るぎなき覚悟したため
If I'm a hero, then I've prepared unwavering resolve,
繰り出せ鉄拳
so I'll unleash my fists!
参上！Go on！正々堂々！！
Appearing! Go on! Fair and square!!
なんだってんだ？もはや敵居ねぇ！
What's happening? My enemies are gone now!
JUSTICE！執行！問答無用！
Justice! Enforcement! No use arguing about it!
俺が断つ！！悪を断つ！！合掌！！
I'll cut off evil!! Hands together in prayer!!
Power! Get power! アドレナリン溢れ出すぜ！
Power! Get power! Adrenaline's overflowing!
Power! Get power! 鍛えた技をぶちかませ！
Power! Get power! Strike hard with tempered technique!
Hero どんなに強い奴も ちっぽけなガキだったんだ
Hero, no matter how strong the enemy, they used to be tiny brats!
Hero 弱き己乗り越え強くなる
Hero, I overcome my weak self and get stronger!
Nobody knows who he is.
神宿る拳掲げて 俺は突き進むだけさ
Raising fists with gods dwelling in them, I'll just plunge forward!
Hero いつか敗北に泥舐めるまで
Hero, until someday I taste the dirt in defeat,
闘うHero
a fighting hero!
俺は諦めない その胸に未来を描き
I won't give up. I picture the future in that heart,
目覚め行く世界へ今 舞い上がれ強く高く
soar up into the awakening world now, stronger, higher!
どんな時でも なにがあっても
No matter what, no matter what happens...
Hero 俺を讃える声や 喝采なんて欲しくはないさ
Hero, I don't want voices praising me or acclamation,
Hero だから人知れず
Hero, that's why I fight in secret.
だから人知れず悪と闘う
That's why I fight evil in secret.
Nobody knows
神宿る拳掲げて
Raising fists with gods dwelling in them,
俺は突き進むだけさ
I'll just plunge forward.
ヒーロー いつか敗北に汚泥なめるまで
Hero, until someday I taste the dirt in defeat,
戦うヒーロー
a fighting hero.
孤独なヒーロー
A lonely hero.
I wanna be a 最強ヒーロー
I wanna be the strongest hero!
This game
[Title: This game]
回り続ける
These spinning cogs
歯車には成り下がらない
show no sign of stopping.
平均演じる
Playing it average,
誕生から始まった地獄
a hell that started from birth.
遊び半分で神が導いた盤上の世界
A world on a board where God playfully led us,
no no no game no life
no, no, game no life!
ぬるい平穏をばさり切り捨てて
cutting away our lukewarm peace
栄光への階段に存在刻むんだ
and engraving our existence on the stairway to glory!
目に映るのは完全勝利の運命
What reflects in our eyes is the destiny of absolute victory.
何もかも計算どおり 変えてやる染まらない空白で
Everything is as calculated. We'll change it with an untainted blank!
we are maverick 救済なんていらない
We are maverick, we don't need a savior!
どんな理不尽襲おうとも 勝てばいいだけの話だろう
No matter how unfair the odds, all that matters is winning!
駆け引きと才能が無敗誘う 生まれ直した命で楽しむさ
Strategy and talent invite invincibility. Let's enjoy our reborn lives!
自分だけは自分信じてる
Believing only in ourselves.
心に潜む闇より強い相手はいない
There is no opponent stronger than the darkness in our hearts,
挫けぬ限りにそこに敗北は有り得ない
and as long as we don't yield, defeat is impossible!
上辺の個性に安心と引き換えにプライド殺すな no no no sense of life
Don't kill your pride for superficial ease, no, no, no sense of life!
野蛮な雑音をけっぱり蹴飛ばして誰より純粋な声上げるんだ
Kick aside the barbaric noise and raise the purest voice of all!
戦うことはきっと間違いじゃない
Fighting is surely not a mistake,
手応えが教えてくれた
as our responsiveness has taught us.
全て失っても勝ち残れ
Win through even if you lose everything!
we are maverick 常識なんていらない 前へならえ向かう先に
We are maverick, we don't need common sense! Marching straight ahead,
待ってんのは退屈だろ 言いなりじゃつまらない挑んでやる
what awaits us is boredom. Taking orders is lame—let's challenge it!
生まれ直した命も駒にして二人だけの道を最後まで迷わぬ選ばし者
Using our reborn lives as pawns, the chosen ones walking our own path to the end without hesitation!
迷わない選ばし者 真っ赤なぬれぼでも誇らしく
Unwavering, chosen ones, proudly living out even a crimson illusion,
生き抜くための方法を一つしか知らないから
because we only know one way of surviving!
we are maverick 救済なんていらない どんな理不尽襲おうとも勝てばいいだけの話だろう 駆け引きと才能が無敗誘う 生まれな...
We are maverick, we don't need a savior! No matter how unfair the odds, all that matters is winning! Strategy and talent invite invincibility. Reborn...
生まれ直した
Reborn
命で楽しむさ
enjoying life to the fullest.
この世界手にして笑うんだ
Taking this world in our hands and laughing.
We are maverick
最強の maverick gamers
the strongest maverick gamers.
空白ならば 何者にもなれる
As blanks, we can become anything.
二人だけは 自分信じてる
Only the two of us believe in ourselves.
御伽話は
The fairy tale
さっき死んだみたい
seems to have died just now
煉瓦の病棟で
in the brick hospital ward,
うまく歌えなくて
unable to sing well,
霧に煙る夜
on a night hazy with fog,
浮かべ赤い月
a red moon floats.
ほらみて 私を
Look at me, see me,
目を逸らさないで
don't look away.
黒い鉄格子の中で
Inside the black iron bars,
私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born into this world.
悪意の代償を願い 望むがままにお前に
Praying for malice's compensation, just as you desire,
さあ与えよう正義を
Now, I will grant you justice.
壊して 壊される前に
Destroy before you are destroyed.
因果の代償を払い 共に行こう
Pay the price of karma and let's go together,
名前のない怪物
nameless monster.
耳鳴りがしてる
There's a ringing in my ears,
鉄条網うるさくて
and the barbed wire is too loud.
思い出せないの
I can't remember
あの日の旋律
the melody of that day.
雨はまだ止まない
The rain still hasn't stopped,
何にも見えないの
and I can't see anything at all.
ほらみて こんなに
Look, see how much
大きくなったの
I've grown.
黒い雨降らせこの空
Bring black rain to this sky,
私は望まれないもの
I am an unwanted being.
ひび割れたノイローゼ 愛す同罪の傍観者達に
To the cracking neurosis and my fellow complicit onlookers,
さあ今ふるえ正義を
Now tremble, unleash justice,
消せない傷を抱きしめて
embracing the unhealable scars.
この身体を受け入れ 共に行こう
Accept this body and let's go together,
名前のない怪物
nameless monster.
ああ
Ah...
神ハ 告ゲル 真ノ世界ヲ
God proclaims the true world.
黒い鉄格子の中で 私は生まれてきたんだ
Inside the black iron bars, I was born into this world.
悪意の代償を願い 望むがままにお前に
Praying for malice's compensation, just as you desire,
さあ与えよう正義を
Now, I will grant you justice.
壊して 壊される前に
Destroy before you are destroyed.
因果の代償を払い
Pay the price of karma
名もなき怪物 黒い雨
nameless monster, black rain...
黒い雨降らせこの空
Black rain, fall from this sky,
私は望まれないもの
I am an unwanted thing.
ひび割れたノイローゼ
A cracked neurosis.
愛す同罪の傍観者達に
To my beloved, equally guilty bystanders,
さあ今震え正義を
now, tremble, ye justice!
消せない傷を抱きしめて
Embracing unerasable scars,
この身体を受け入れ
accepting this body,
共に行こう
let's go together,
名前のない怪物
nameless monster.
教えて 教えてよ その仕組みを
Teach me, teach me, how does this work?
僕の中に 誰がいるの？
Who is inside me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
I'm broken, so broken in this world,
君が笑う 何も見えずに
while you laugh, seeing nothing at all.
壊れた僕なんてさ
A broken me,
息を止めて
stopping my breath.
ほどけない もうほどけないよ
I can't unravel—no, I can't unravel,
真実さえ freeze
even the truth—freeze.
壊せる 壊せない
Can I break it? Can't break it?
狂える 狂えない
Go mad? Can't go mad?
あなたを見つけて 揺れた
Finding you, I trembled.
歪んだ世界に だんだん僕は透き通って
In a distorted world, I slowly turn transparent,
見えなくなって 見つけないで
vanishing from sight. Please don't find me,
僕のことを見つめないで
don't look at me.
誰かが描いた 世界の中で
Inside a world someone painted,
あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
I don't want to hurt you.
覚えていて 僕のことを
Please remember me.
鮮やかなまま
As vivid as I am.
無限に広がる 孤独が絡まる
Endlessly expanding solitude entangles me,
無邪気に笑った 記憶が刺さって
memories of innocent laughter pierce deep.
動けない 動けない 動けない 動けないよ
I can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move!
unravelling the world
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
What changed could not be changed back,
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
two things entwine, two people perish.
壊せる 壊せない
Can I break it? Can't break it?
狂える 狂えない
Go mad? Can't go mad?
あなたを汚せないよ 揺れた
I won't defile you, I trembled.
歪んだ世界に だんだん僕は透き通って
In a distorted world, I slowly turn transparent,
見えなくなって 見つけないで
vanishing from sight. Please don't find me,
僕のことを見つめないで
don't look at me.
誰かが仕組んだ 孤独な罠に
Into a lonely trap someone set,
未来がほどけてしまう前に
before the future comes unraveled,
思い出して 僕のことを
please remember me.
鮮やかなまま
As vivid as I am,
忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで
don't forget, don't forget, don't forget, don't forget!
変わってしまったことに paralyze
Paralyzed by the fact that everything changed,
変えられないことだらけの paradise
a paradise full of things we cannot change.
覚えていて 僕のことを
Please remember me.
教えて 教えてよ その仕組みを
Teach me, teach me, how does this work?
僕の中に 誰がいるの？
Who is inside me?
はーい、みんな、ここまで楽しんでみてもらえましたか？
Hi everyone, did you enjoy it up to here?
そして、なんと気づいたときにはもうホロウィッチ！の衣装に着替えしていましたー！
And, what do you know, by the time you noticed, I had already changed into my HoloWitch! outfit!
どうでしょうか？いや、もともと可愛いのに、さらに可愛くなったというか、可愛さは変わらないままというか、ね？素敵な衣装ですね。
What do you think? I mean, I was already cute, but I became even cuter... Right? It's a wonderful outfit.
はーい、さてさてみんな、最初に話した重大告知、覚えてる？
Alright, so everyone, do you remember the important announcement I talked about at the beginning?
気になってたよね、ちゃんと今までずっとね。
You've been curious all this time, right?
いやあ、でも、うーん、どうしよっかなあ。いや、やめとこっかなあ。いやどうしよっかなあ。やめとこっかなあ。
Well, but, hmm, what should I do? No, maybe I should stop. Well, what should I do? Maybe I should stop.
はい、というわけで、じゃあ今日はここまで！ライブ終わり、ありがとうみんな観てくれて。
Yes, so that's all for today! Thank you everyone for watching the end of the live.
まってまってまって！まってまってまって！
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
なんと！紫シオン新しいオリジナル曲が出ます！いえーい！
What! Murasaki Shion's new original song is coming out! Yay!
今回ですね、初めてのアニメーションMVとなっていて、この後ライブ後にプレミアム公開されます。
This time, it's my first animated MV, and it will premiere right after the live.
さらに、本日の24時各音楽配信サイトにてリリースされます！
Furthermore, it will be released on various music streaming sites today at 24:00!
プレミアム公開の後にはメンバー限定でミニライブもあるのでよかったら見てください。メンバー入ってる方もね、入ってない方もこれを気にちょっと見ていただけたらなと思っております。
After the premium premiere, there's a mini-live for members, so please check it out if you'd like.
どうでしょうか？
How was that?
はい、ふふ。はい、というわけで曲の後にはあの告知もあるのでお楽しみに！
Yes, haha. Yes, so after the song, there's that announcement too, so look forward to it!
最後の曲はさっき言ったオリ曲を初披露です。ピノキオピーさんに書き下ろしていただきました。曲名は『ごめんねメディスン』です。
The last song is the first performance of the original song written by Pinocchio-P, titled "Gomen ne Medicine."
変身できる 変身できちゃうから
I can transform, because I can transform,
今日も生意気に笑ってる
today too, I'm smiling impudently.
調合してる 調合していたのは
What I was mixing, what I was mixing
君を癒せる薬
was medicine to heal you.
この薬草ちょっと苦いから やめとこうくりかえして
This medicinal herb is a bit bitter, so repeating "let's stop,"
このキノコはなんかヤバイけど まあいっか！後悔して
this mushroom is somehow dangerous, but whatever! Regretting it,
ちょっと擦りむいた傷 隠したセンシティブ
a slightly scraped wound, hiding the sensitive parts,
「なんでもないよ…」無限にあるけど
saying "It's nothing..." though it's infinite,
めっちゃ伝えたい伝えたいんだ好きを
I want so badly to convey my love,
でも言えない言えないや恥ずかしいもん
but I can't, I can't, it's too embarrassing!
君を想って作った薬が
The medicine I made thinking of you
毒になったらゴメンねメディスン
turning into poison—sorry, medicine.
ゴメンねメディスン
Sorry, medicine.
ちゃんとありがとうが言えなくて
Being unable to properly say "Thank you,"
届け 届け 君に
reach, reach, to you,
わたしの メディスン
my medicine.
ああやったらこうなっちゃうな そうなったらしょうがないな
Ah, if I do that, it turns out like this—if so, it can't be helped.
予想外の副作用 ガツンと食っちゃわ
The unexpected side effect hits me hard!
イメージ イメージ 君の笑顔アメージング
Image, image—your smile is amazing,
でも涙が混ざっちゃう パーセンテージ
but tears get mixed in, percentage.
用法とはちょっと違うから ちゃんとしようと思ったり
Since it's a bit different from the instructions, thinking I should do it right,
用量がわかんなくなっても なんとか慣れと祈ったり
even if I don't know the dosage, praying it will somehow work out,
ハッと気がついたミス 飛んでった楽園気分
suddenly realizing a mistake, my paradise mood flying away,
「どうでもいいよ…」すごい気になるけど
saying "Whatever..." though I care so much,
魔法唱えたいんだ熱いの
I want to cast a spell—it's hot,
でも冷たい態度は怖いよ
but a cold attitude is scary!
ノリで作ったファジーな薬が
A fuzzy medicine made on a whim,
合わなかったらゴメンねメディスン
if it doesn't match—sorry, medicine.
ゴメンねメディスン
Sorry, medicine.
冗談でごまかしてばかりで
Always smoothing things over with jokes,
後悔して後悔してもう一度
regretting it, regretting it, once more,
めっちゃ伝えたい伝えたいんだ好きを
I want so badly to convey my love,
でも言えない言えないや恥ずかしいもん
but I can't, I can't, it's too embarrassing!
君を想って作った薬が
The medicine I made thinking of you
毒になったらゴメンねメディスン
turning into poison—sorry, medicine.
ゴメンねメディスン
Sorry, medicine.
ちゃんとありがとうが言えなくて
Being unable to properly say "Thank you,"
届け 届け 君に
reach, reach, to you,
わたしの メディスン
my medicine.
不器用な メディスン
Clumsy medicine,
素直になれなくって
unable to be honest,
ゴメンね メディスン
sorry, medicine.
「いつもありがとう」って
Saying "Thank you always,"
「ずっと一緒にいよう」って
saying "Let's be together forever,"
ちゃんと言えなくって 溶けちゃったメディスン
unable to say it properly—medicine that melted away.
ゴメンね メディスン
Sorry, medicine.
ちゃんと届いている？
Is it properly reaching you?
ちゃんと届いてる？
Is it reaching you properly?
みんな、紫咲シオンバースデー記念生ライブ
Everyone, thank you for watching the
Murasaki Shion Birthday Live
最後まで見てくれてありがとう！
until the very end!
最後に、誕生日記念グッズのお知らせです。
Lastly, I have an announcement
about the birthday commemorative goods!
紫咲シオン誕生日記念グッズ2024がでます！
The Murasaki Shion Birthday
Commemorative Goods 2024 are out!
もうすでにね、今出ちゃってるイラストが可愛すぎるよね！
The illustration shown right now
is just way too cute, isn't it?!
それでは、1個ずつ見ていきましょう！
Now let's take a look
at them one by one!
まずはこちら、キャンバスアート！初めて出すよね、キャンバスアート。
First is this, the canvas art!
It's my first time releasing canvas art.
イラストはりいちゅ先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn
by Riichu-sensei!
現代のキラキラ魔法少女がテーマのキービジュアルです。めっっちゃ可愛いし、
It's a key visual themed around a
modern sparkling magical girl. Super cute,
さすがに世界救ってそうだよよね！しおっこもいてかわいいね！
and she totally looks like she's going
to save the world! Little Shions are cute!
そしてお次は こちら、マルチケース！イラストは夢乃うち先生に描いていただきました。
Next up is this, the multi-case!
Drawn by Yumeno Uchi-sensei.
いやあこれもね、可愛すぎる！ゲーミング衣装のシオンとなってます。
Man, this is also way too cute!
Featuring Shion in her gaming outfit.
なんとね、付いてるラバーパーツ、このキーホルダーみたいなやつがね、取り外し可能で別々でも使えちゃうんです！
And get this, the rubber keychain parts
can be detached and used separately!
一緒につけるもよし、別のアイテムと合わせてもよしな可愛すぎるアイテム！
You can attach them together or match
them with other items—super cute!
クリアになってるから入れてるものが見えてめちゃ可愛いですね。推し活に向いているかなと思います。
It's clear so you can see inside.
Great for oshi-katsu (supporting your favorite).
ぜひ手に入れてね！
Please make sure to get one!
はい、そしてお次は こちら、スマホショルダー ストラップ！可愛いビーズがついてます！
Next is this smartphone shoulder strap!
It comes with cute beads!
いっぱい可愛いのがついててね、色も可愛くてめちゃおしゃれで実用的となってます。
Lots of cute things attached, cute colors,
super stylish, and practical.
これつけてね、たくさんお出かけしてほしいですね、みんなこれ首から下げてね！ぜひよろしくお願いします！
I'd love for you to wear this and go out,
everyone hanging this from your neck!
そしてまだまだあります！次はこちら、シオンとおそろい刺繍Tシャツ！
And there's still more! Next is this
Shion-matching embroidered T-shirt!
いやあね、みんなね、ゲーミング衣装のTシャツが欲しいって新衣装を出したときにいっぱい言ってもらったので、なんと今回ね、刺繍で再現しちゃいました！フル刺繍になってます、これね。
You guys wanted the gaming outfit T-shirt,
so this time we reproduced it with embroidery!
It's full embroidery!
あのプリントじゃなくて、だからめっちゃクオリティ高いです！あの、おしゃれすぎ、本当に着てておしゃれすぎる！シオンもこれたくさん着ま、買います、自分で。
It's not print, so the quality is super high!
It's so stylish to wear! I'll buy lots too.
ぜひ手にとって確かめてみてください！めっちゃ本当にクオリティめっちゃ高いから、絶対手に入れてほしい！本当にTシャツぜひお願いします！
Please check it out! The quality is really
high, so I definitely want you to get it!
Please get the T-shirt!
そして最後ですね、シチュエーションボイスとなっております。
And lastly, we have the
situation voice pack.
いや、あの、絶対手に入れてほしいてたくさん言ったけどね、全部手に入れてほしいからね！
Well, I said you should definitely get it,
but I want you to get all of them!
はい、そして最後はフルセットの紹介です。今回フルセットを購入してくれた人に、数量限定で直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドがついてきます！数量限定です、ごめんなさい！
And last is the full set introduction.
Full set buyers get a signed cheki-style bromide!
Limited quantity, sorry!
え、でもみんなのためにサイン頑張るので、あの、よかったらお手に取ってもらえたらなと思っております。数量限定です、ごめんなさい！
But I'll work hard signing for everyone,
so I hope you can pick one up. Limited quantity!
さらにフルセット購入特典がもう1つあります。ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付きます！特典につくのは推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。カードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご容赦ください。
There's another full-set bonus.
You get a hololive official card game card!
A key holo-member card. Japanese version only.
はい、というわけでここまで告知してきましたが、誕生日記念グッズは配信終了後に販売開始されます！概要欄にURLがあるので、シオンのTwitterを見て確認してもらえたらなと思います。
Alright, that's all for the announcements.
The birthday goods go on sale after the stream!
Check Shion's Twitter for the link.
よろしくお願いします！数量限定だからね！
Thank you! Because it's limited quantity!
そろそろ終わりの時間が来てしまいますが、このあとオリジナル曲MVの公開と、メンゲンでミニライブをやるので、よかったら遊びに来てください！お願いします、待ってます！
It's almost time to wrap up, but after this
is the MV premiere and a membership mini live!
Please come join us!
それではみんな今日は最後までありがとうございました！素敵な誕生日でした！ありがとー！
Alright everyone, thank you so much for today!
It was a wonderful birthday! Thank you!